Everyone wants to do it... but only a few dare
Educating Julie is a drama, documentary film directed by Gail Hardman.
Julie is an English student assigned to write a paper about "nudity in the 80s".
A bit overwhelmed at first she takes on the project by
visiting a nudist camping with her boyfriend.
But while she learns about nudity and nudism, her
boyfriend struggles to keep up.
Julie Potter, played by Gail Ward.
Steve, played by Miles Taylor.
Tony, played by Tony Monroe.
Mike, played by Gary Willock.
Tutor, played by Anthony Schaeffer.
Shop Assistant, played by Angie Shaw Wright.
Educating Rita is a 1983 British comedy-drama film directed by Lewis Gilbert
with a screenplay by Willy Russell based on his 1980 stage play.
The film stars Michael Caine, Julie Walters,
Michael Williams and Maureen Lipman.
It won multiple major awards for best actor and best actress
and was nominated for three Academy Awards.
Caine and Walters both won BAFTA and Golden Globe
awards for best actor and actress.
The British Film Institute ranked Educating Rita the 84th
greatest British film of the 20th century.
The film explores themes of research, england, interview, travel, nudism.
The tone is emotional.